Dean, have you got a moment?
Dean, 你有空吗?
Sure. I'm on my way home.
有的. 我在回家的路上.
I'm working on a scheme to attract younger customers.
我正在做一个方案 来吸引年轻的顾客.
To the restaurant?
(吸引)到餐厅?
Yes.
是的
"Youth Market Trends in the Dining Industry".
"年轻人的市场发展趋势  在餐饮业"
I beg your pardon?
请再说一遍?
My research last semester was on this topic.
我上一学期的研究  就是这个话题.
Do go on.
继续说.
Well, in general, younger customers prefer casual dining.
Well, 总的来说, 年轻的顾客更喜欢休闲的进餐.
Yes.
是的.
They like finger food.
他们喜欢手指食物(finger food).
In fact, they often order appetizers.
事实上, 他们经常会点开胃菜(appetizers)
In the bar, they prefer beer and wine to hard liquor.
在酒吧, 他们喜欢啤酒和红酒胜过烈性酒.
Is that information useful?
那信息有用吗?
Absolutely. Let me ask you a question.
绝对地. 让我问你一个问题.
Do they prefer large portions?
他们喜欢更大的分量吗?
I mean, is that important?
我的意思是, 那重要吗?
Sure. They like large portions,
是的. 他们喜欢更大的分量,
but they prefer lower prices.
但是他们更喜欢便宜的价格.
After all, they're not making much money yet!
毕竟, 他们还赚不了多少钱!
Is that the voice of experience, Dean?
那是经验之谈吗, Dean?
Highly researched, of course.
深入地调查后的(结论), 当然了.